

Lasantha Attanayake Web Developer

I'm a graduate of Sri Lanka Institute of Information Technology with more than five years working experience as a web based developer and an engineer .Able to work on own initiative or as part of a team and make every endeavor to fulfill the duties entrusted to me. Also I am a good team player and fast learner.

Telephone +94(0)716178231 | +94(0)777365051

Email lasantha_attanayake@yahoo.com

Address No.284,Embilmeegama,Pilimatalawa, 20450

Skills | Tools

Web Design / Development

HTML - 8/10 , CSS - 7/10

Bootstrap - 7/10, LESS - 6/10

Responsive web development - 8/10

Adobe Photoshop - 5/10

Javascript / JQuery / Ajax - 7/10

PHP - 7/10 , MySql - 7/10

CMS

Wordpress – 8/10 Woocommerce – 5/10 Magento 2 – 6/10

API

Facebook - 6/10 , WP-Rest - 2/10

<u>Version Control</u> Git , Svn / Stash, Bitbucket

<u>Personal Interest</u>

Develop and design the web based product using PHP and MySql based CMSs and Frameworks.

Professional Experience

	,
01 st Dec 2016 -	 Software Engineer One Soft International Guide and Handle Wordpress project and maintenance. Magento Theme, module development and maintenance. Magento 2/Magento 2 Cloud / Wordpress / Html / CSS / JQuery / Git / Jira / Bit Bucket
12 th Feb 2016 to 31 st Oct 2016	PHP Engineer – Mazarin (Pvt) Ltd Contract Agreement. > Wordpress / HTML / CSS / JQuery / woocommerce
18 th June 2014 to 30 th Dec 2015	Senior Web Developer eMarketingEye (Pvt) Ltd > Web development and web maintenance > Wordpress / HTML / CSS / LESS / Bootstrap / JQuery / SVN / Git / Stash
01 st Sep 2011 to 30 th Nov 2013	Senior Web Developer Looops Solutions (Pvt) Ltd. Facebook Canvas Applications development, Web development, web maintenance, Hosting PHP / MySql / JQuery / Ajax / Joomla / CakePHP / Wordpress / Facebook API / TortoiseGit
01 st July 2010 to 31 st Aug 2011	Software Engineer Softknowedge Business Solutions (Pvt) Ltd. PHP Based ERP Applications Development PHP / MySql / Ajax / SVN

Education

2005- 2008	Sri Lanka Institute of Information Technology BSc.sp (Hons) in Information Technology
2010	Turn Key IT Training Institute Linux administration with security Diploma
2007	Golden Key Institute of Computer Technology Ltd. Advanced Web Developing Diploma PHP/MySql,ASP.Net
1989 - 2004	Kingswood College – Kandy GCE O/L & GCE A/L (Agriculture Science)

Academic Project Experiences

2006 Pharmacy Registration System for Food & Drugs Authority,

Sri Lanka.- VB.Net 2003/MS.SQL Server 2000/ Crystal

Reports

2008 Prototype web application for SLIIT course web. - PHP/MySql

2008 Simple Stock Controlling System for Luxmi Metaal Stock &

Selling Company.- VB.Net 2005/MS.SQL Server 2000) /

Prototype-PHP/MySql

2008 Final year project "Extending the Programming Tool for

Sinhala Developers" - C#.Net 2005

Personnel Details

Full Name Attanayake Mudiyansela Lasantha Kanchana Attanayake.

Date of Birth 23-08-1983
Age 35 years
Sex Male
Civil status Single
Nationality Sri Lankan
NIC No 832361364V

Extra-curricular Activities

Scouting 2001-President Scout

Boxing ➤ 1998 - L.V.Jayaweera memorial cup (under 43kg) 2nd

runner up

> 1998 - T.B.Jaya memorial cup (under 45kg) 2nd runner

ир

≥ 2000 - Junior national boxing meet (under 48kg) 2nd

runner up

➤ 2002 - Captain of the school boxing team.

Referees

Mr. Himira Ratnatilake. Mr. Thiwanka Dodanwela. Information Systems Architect Technical Lead - Front End

ICT Agency of Sri Lanka Development
ISM APAC

160/24, Kirimandala Mawatha,

Colombo 05, Sri Lanka 752, Dr. Danister De Silva Mw, E-Mail :- himirar@icta.lk Colombo 09, Sri Lanka

Tel:- Mobile - +94(0)77360510 Tel:- Mobile - +94(0)718026132

I do hereby certify that the above details are true and correct according to the best of my knowledge.

......